It was quite an arduous project to help every mage, who had just awakened magic or only had two or three elements, to master it proficiently. There were too many factors to consider. They had to ensure that the Fusion Magic was suitable for everyone and in no way posed any harm to them.

At first, Mo Fan thought that the promotion of Fusion Magic would be carried out at the university. Later, he found out that the Fusion Magic was best carried out by people who had just awakened their magic so that they could learn the profound meaning of the magic from the beginning. In this way, it would be easier for them to control the energy of the two attributes after they had the second element awakened.